Guide to the George Mason University Libraries records, 1949-2008
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 4: Committees and collaborations, 1960-2004
  - Arlington county library, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Artistic and Cultural Programming and Activities group, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Arts Task Force, Fine Arts Commission, 1983 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Association of College and Research Libraries (ACRL), EBSS Conference Program Planning Committee, New Orleans, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Association of College and Research Libraries (ACRL), 1994-1995 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Bibliographic control of maps in Fenwick Library subcommittee, 1981-1983 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Board of visitors, 1978-1979 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Board of visitors, 1978-1994 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Bookstore Advisory Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Campus development historical files, 1990-1991 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Campus development project team, 1990-1991 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Campus Wide Information Working group (CWIS), 1993 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Campus Wide Information Working group (CWIS), 1993 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Campus Wide Information Working group (CWIS), general, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Campus Wide Information Working group (CWIS), 1993 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    Memos, minutes, notes
  - Campus Wide Information Working group (CWIS), 1993 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Campus Wide Information Working group (CWIS), organization subcommittee, 1993 August 24 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Campus Wide Information Working group (CWIS), 1993 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    Organization subcommittee draft menus
  - Committee on Committees, 1978-1979 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Committees, 1979-1980 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Committees, 1980-1981 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Committees, 1981-1982 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Committees, 1982-1983 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Committees, 1983-1984 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Committees, 1984-1985 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Committees, 1985-1986 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Committees, 1986-1987 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Committees, 1987-1988 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Committees, Librarians' handbook (revision), 1988 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Committees, elections, 1988-1989 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Committees, bylaws, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Committees, 1989-1990 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Committees, 1990-1991 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Committees, 1991-1992 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA), 1977-1978 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Computer and Information Systems Committees, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Computer and Information Systems Committees, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Consortia articles, 1970s (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Consortium, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), 1978 June 30 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), 1978 June 30 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), 1978-1982 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), 1978-1982 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), 1995 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), The Consort (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), Library Networking Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), Library Networking Committee, Automation subcommittee, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), Library Networking Committee, community resources proposal, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), Library Networking Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), Library Networking Committee, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), miscellaneous exchange program, 1981-1983 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education (CCHENV), Consortium NVCC, Annandale, 1976-1984 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Coordinating task force Committees, undated (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Consortium of Universities, Washington area taskforces, 1986-1996 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Department of Education, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Distance, Distributed Learning Committee group, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Documents delivery task force, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Documents delivery task force, 1991-1993 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Educational Planning Committee, 1978 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Electronic reserve task force, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Facilities and Support Services Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Committee on the library, Charge from the provost, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Committee on the library, 1988-1989 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Committee on the library, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Committee, Kathy Gaffney, Graduate library, 1989 February (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Faculty handbook, Steering Committee, 1984 February 1 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Faculty handbook, 1984-1994 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Library Committee, notes, 1960-1976 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Library Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Senate Library Committee, miscellaneous, 1968-1972 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Senate Library Committee, 1976 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Senate Library Committee, 1976 September-1978 September (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Senate Library Committee, 1976 September-1978 September (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Senate Library Committee, 1978 September-December (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate Library Committee, 1988 Fall (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Senate Library Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Senate Library Committee, 1997 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Senate handbook, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Senate, University facilities and support service, 1976-1977 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Senate, University file, 1987-1992 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Feminist round table, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Fenwick library space planning task force, 1999-2000s (Box 84, Folder 7)
    Survey of staff space
  - Food Service Advisory Committee, personnel matters, general, 1985-1986 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Foundation gifts, 1996-1997 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Friends of the Library, 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Friends of the Library, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Friends of the Library, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Friends of the Library, Agronsky event, 1980 April 29 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Friends of the Library, background, preliminary planning, 1978-1981 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Friends of the Library, book sale, 1980-1982 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Friends of the Library, brochure, undated (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Friends of the Library, membership, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Friends of the Library, membership and membership letter, 1981-1982 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Friends of the Library, membership list, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Friends of the Library, 1979-1980 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    Minutes and correspondence
  - Friends of the Library, 1980s (Box 85, Folder 14)
    Programs
  - General Education task force, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - General faculty, 1991-1994 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - George Mason University Press, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - George Mason University Press, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - George Mason University Press, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - George Mason University Press, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Governance Review Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    Library governance revision memos
  - Government, Society and the Arts, "New Deal" and subcommittees, 1976-1980 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Government, Society and the Arts, 1979-1980 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Government, Society and the Arts, 1981-1983 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Grassroots campaign, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Human resources for technology implementation (Chris Dede working group), 1993 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Inauguration Advisory Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Information Center Committee union III, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Information resources project team, 1980s (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Information Resources and Intellectual Access (IRIA), 2000-2001 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    Action agenda
  - IT Committee report, 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Information Technology and Education group, 1993 April (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Information Networking Committee, 1991-1996 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Information Technology Planning Committee, 1997 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Institute for Educational Transformation (IET), 1995-1996 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    Faculty Senate materials
  - Institute for Information Technology (GMIIT), 1983-1987 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - International programs Committee, 1978-1983 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Joanne Johnson and Gala Committee, 1986 June 17 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Learning Initiatives Project team, 1989-1991 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Learning Initiatives Project team, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Learning Initiatives Project team subcommittee, design and delivery, 1990-1992 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Learning Initiatives Project team subcommittee, facilities, 1990-1991 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), article about work of task force, 2000-2001 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), charge, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), discussion meetings about final report with task force and professional library staff, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), faculty focus groups, 2001-2002 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2001-2002 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    Faculty survey
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2002 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    Final report with appendices
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2002 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    Final report executive summary with notes
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2004 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    Liaison task force completion letter from John Zenelis
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2002 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    Letter to faculty, survey and lists of faculty
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2001-2002 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    Powerpoint introducing LLPTF to entire UL staff at all staff meeting
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2001-2002 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Questions and summary of interviews with Faculty Senate Library Committee
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2002 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    Questions to liaisons and department heads and summary
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2002 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    Statistical analysis of faculty survey
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), student focus groups, 2002 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2001-2002 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    Summary analysis faculty survey
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2001-2002 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    Working papers, agendas, minutes, notes
  - Liaison Librarian Program task force (LLPTF), 2002 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    Works consulted
  - Librarians council, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Librarians council, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Librarians council, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Librarians council, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Librarians council, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Librarians council, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Librarians council, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Librarians council, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Librarians council, 1982-1985 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Librarians council, 1985-1996 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Librarians council, 1988-1989 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Librarians council (Posner), 1984-1992 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Librarians council (Posner), 1988-2000 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Librarians council (Posner), 1982-1991 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Librarians council (Posner), 1978-1998 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Librarians council, Annual Reports Committee, 1978-1982 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Librarians council, Appointments Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Librarians council, bylaws amended, 1978 September 5 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Librarians council, bylaws, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Librarians council, 1976-1981 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    Committee on Committees correspondence,
  - Librarians council, committees, 1980-1990 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Librarians council, evaluation and promotion, 1975-1978 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Librarians council, evaluation and promotion, 1978-1982 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Librarians council, evaluation and promotion evaluations, 1982-1987 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 1976-1977 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Librarians council, Handbook governance, 1976-1983 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Librarians council, 1976-1989 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    Handbook, memos, issues, revisions
  - Librarians council, handbook, new Ad Hoc Committee revision, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Librarians council, handbook, fourth draft amended, 1977 May (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Librarians council, handbook, historic material, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 1981-1982 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 1982-1983 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 1980 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Librarians council, handbook drafts, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 1987 November 20 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 1989 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 1989 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 1989-1992 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Librarians council, handbook, meetings, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Librarians council, handbook, revisions, 1999-2000 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Librarians council, handbook, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Librarians council, handbook Committee correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Librarians council, Instruction Committee, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Librarians council, Media Committee, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Librarians council, minutes, 1975-1977 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Librarians council, minutes, 1975-1977 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Librarians council, minutes, 1978-1983 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Librarians council, minutes, 1978-1983 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Librarians council, minutes, 1978-1983 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Librarians council, minutes, handbook, 1982-2000 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Librarians council, minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Librarians council, minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Librarians council, Council meeting, 1995 March 9 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Librarians council, Planning and Policy Committee, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Librarians council, Professional Development Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Library Automation Advisory Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Library Committee meeting, 1989 March 22 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Library Instruction Planning group, 1997 May 1 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Library of Virginia, Library Services and Construction Act (LSCA), 1989 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Library Staff Association, 1982-1985 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Library task force, 1988 November (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Library task force, Library subcommittee, graduate and professional school needs (Kathy), 1989 February 8 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Library task force, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Lobby Beautification Committee, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Major and special events programming and activities planning group, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Management group, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Marcive project, 1989-1990 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Mason and University Scholars, 1990-1994 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Mason Link, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Media Committee (LIPT file), 1991 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Morino Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Morino Foundation, 1994-1996 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Multi-cultural international programming and activities, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - National faculty exchange, 1986-1992 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - National library week, 1964-1967 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - National Technology Center, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - New Century College, zero based curriculum, 1993-1994 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - New Century College, zero based curriculum, 1993-1997 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Northern Virginia Institute, data services center, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Northern Virginia Library Networking council, 1980-1992 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Northern Virginia (NOVA) public school partnerships, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - NOTIS, 1989-1994 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - NOTIS, 1990-1994 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - NOTIS, advisory group, 1982-1993 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - NOTIS, budget, 1988-1989 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - NOTIS, budget, 1989-1995 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - NOTIS, Central library transition team, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - NOTIS, Central library transition team, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - NOTIS, Central library transition team, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - NOTIS, Central library transition team, 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - NOTIS, CH, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - NOTIS, dealings, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - NOTIS, library systems transition team, 1988-1989 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - NOTIS, library systems transition team, 1989-1990 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - NOTIS, MDAS program, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - NOTIS, MDAS Virginia proposal, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - NOTIS, MDAS WRLC, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - NOTIS, MDAS WRLC, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - NOTIS, sublicense agreement, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - NOTIS, training, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - NOTIS, users group meeting, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - OCLC, 1995 May 21-23 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - OCLC, 1996 May 19-21 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - OCLC, Communications and Access Interest Group, 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - OCLC, local systems, 1988-1994 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - OCLC, local systems, 1984-1987 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - OCLC, meeting, 1996 October 6-8 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - OCLC, users council file (historical file), 1994 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - OCLC, users council file (historical file), 1996 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - OCLC, users council meeting - Dublin, Ohio, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - OCLC, users council meeting - Dublin, Ohio, 1995 January 23-25 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Patriot Center Advisory Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Planning Committee, physical facilities, library III, 1979-1980 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Planning groups, undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Planning and Policy Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Planning and Review Committee, Word processing, 1977-1982 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Policy and Planning council, 1981-1994 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Policy and Planning council, 1986-1990 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Policy and Planning council, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Policy and Planning council, 1986-1987 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Policy and Planning council, 1987-1990 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Policy and Planning council, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Policy and Planning council, 1989-1990 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Policy and Planning council, 1991-1993 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Policy and Planning council, 1994-1995 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Policy and Planning council, 1994-1995 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Policy and Procedure Committee of the Research and Planning council, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - President's council, George Johnson, Executive council, 1982-1985 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - President's council, George Johnson, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - President's council, 1994-1995 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - President's council, 1996 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - President's council, 1997 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - President's file, Saturday morning planning sessions, 1985-1988 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - President Johnson's file, executive council, 1987-1991 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Prince William Planning group, 1990-1991 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Procedures, Salalm secreteriat, 1978-1980 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Professional Development Committee, 1981-1991 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    Annual report
  - Professional Review Committee, 1989-1992 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Professional Review Committee, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Professional Review Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Public policy, Joseph L. Fisher, 1987-1988 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Publications Committee (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Reaffirmation Committee, Commission on Colleges, 2001 April 16-19 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Reference Instructional Services Committee, 1983-2000 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Reference Instructional Services Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Reference Instructional Services Committee, report, 1999-2000 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Research Libraries group, 1989-1980 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Research Planning council, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Research Planning council, 1981-1983 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Research Planning council, 1981-1983 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Research Planning council, Research Facilities and Equipment Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Research Planning council, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Research Planning council, 1984-1985 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Research Planning council, 1985-1986 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Research Planning council, 1986-1987 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Research Planning council, 1988-1992 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Robinson subcommittee on Jack Goldstone, 1993 November (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Salary task force, 1992-1993 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - San Martin society, 1979-1980 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Senate Facilities Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Solinet, 1992-1995 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Solinet, Association for Southeastern Research Libraries, 1989-1996 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Solinet, Board of Directors, 1993-1995 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Solinet, Monticello electronic library, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Solinet, Nominating Committee, 1993-1996 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Solinet, SURA Solinet, 1993 July 9 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Solinet, SURA Solinet meeting in Atlanta, Georgia (Monticello electric library meeting), 1993 July 29-30 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Solinet, SURA Solinet meeting in Atlanta, Georgia, 1994 May 13 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Solinet, Atlanta, Georgia, 1994 February-March (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Solinet, board meeting, Atlanta, Georgia, 1993 December 2-3 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Solinet, fall board meeting, Hyatt Regency, Knoxville, TN, 1993 October 5-8 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Solinet, Stouffer Hotel, Atlanta, Georgia, 1993 August 10 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Solinet, 1993-1996 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Solinet, 1991-1993 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Solinet, 1987-1992 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Solinet, agreement, 1983-1984 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Solinet, regional information network in Solinet group, 1993-1994 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), Commission on colleges, 2001 April (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), distance education, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), reaccreditation compliance report, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 5)